JINNY AN

Graphic/Web Designer Web Developer

+1 647 895 8349 ansujinny@gmail.com

Passionate, creative and confident Graphic Designer with 5 years of full time on-the-job experience ranging from signage, branding to editorial design.

I have been responsible for a webpage, banner, and advertisement designs from concept to final implementation, which allows me to adapt quickly to new and various facets of design material.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FEB . 2020 - CURRENT

Freelance Graphic Designer

- Upon the client's request I produced designs required and suited to their needs from concept to final implementation.
- Produced a variety of logos, editorial, branding and in addition, brochure, business cards and leaflet materials.
- Designed and developed websites using knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JS.

SEP. 2016 - OCT. 2019

Dream S&D Graphic Designer / Hospital Branding and Sign Design

- Responsible for the branding of newly established hospitals and clinics including the logo, exterior signage design, interior signage design, documentation template design business card design, design of hospital marketing material
- Obtained a well-rounded skillset from research, running concept design meeting effective communication skills. project management, site visits, material preparation, site preparation, site/ construction supervision and management.
- Worked closely and directly with clients one on one, sharing innovative ideas and bringing them to life.
 Effective communication skills were developed, most importantly listening and understanding the client's needs.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Hangang Childrens Hospital - Branding Design

Hangang Children's Hospital is a children's hospital with three branches and is the one of the largest hospital in Korea. When this Gimpp branch was first established, I was responsible for the overall brand design, from the hospital's logo to the interior and exterior sign design.

- Role: Graphic Designer
- Client: Hangang Childrens Hospital
- Location: Gimpo, Korea
- Date(s): June 2019 July 2019

Saengki Oriental Clinic - Branding Design

Saengki Oriental Clinic is a new oriental five-story building clinic. Through the design meeting with the hospital, I undertook both the logo of the hospital and the design of the five-story indoor signage.

- Role: Graphic Designer
- Client: Saengki Oriental Clinic
- Location: Seoul, Korea
- Date(s): April 2019

JINNY AN

Graphic/Web Designer Web Developer

+1 647 895 8349 ansujinny@gmail.com

• FEB. 2016 - AUG. 2016

Design Planning & Public Relation Dept Graphic Designer

Designed material for university events, webpage banners, exhibitions, and marketing in general.
 Worked in collaboration with a team, leading meetings and design scope works hopes and finally implementation.

MAY. 2015 - AUG. 2015

Design House Editorial Designer

- Worked on editorials and design of a column for the monthly "Designhouse" magazine.

EDUCATION

JAN. 2022 - AUG. 2022

Humber College Web Design & Development

- Develop applications with JavaScript, including the latest in open-source frameworks and libraries for front-end applications
- Designing and prototyping interactive interfaces using industry standard tools or applications
- Master the latest specifications for HTML & CSS, including accessible content and design

MAR. 2014 - FEB. 2017

Bucheon University Bachelor's Degree of Industrial Design and UI Design

- Obtained a Bachelor's Degree in Industrial design with a focus in the graphic user interface, brand identity and UI & UX design.
- Scholarship during the course of degree for 3 years.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Indesign Time management
Adobe Illustration Adobe After Effects Team player
Adobe XD HTML, CSS, JS Deadline-driven

QUALIFICATIONS

- · Graphic Technology Qualification Photoshop
- Graphic Technology Qualification Illustration



Graphic/Web Designer Web Developer

+1 647 895 8349 ansujinny0@gmail.com

August 8, 2022

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to apply for the position of Web Designer, which was advertised online at Ontario Public Service Careers.

Over the years, I've gained a Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Design at Bucheon University in Korea. In University, I learned not only overall graphic design skills but also, program tool skills such as Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign and also studied UI and UX design. Upon graduating from university, I gained professional experience with 3 years at a signage & graphic design company called "Dream Design", with the recommendation of a professor, and experienced various design projects which are hospital branding design including logo, indoor and outdoor signage, stationery design at the company, growing a lot as a Graphic Designer.

This professional experience has helped me improve my responsibility to lead a design project. From the initial scoping meeting with the client through to design and construction, the experience I gained by leading the project from start to finish helped me obtain leadership, planning, and communication skills.

Having a desire to work in the field as a web designer further, I am currently studying Web Design & Development at Humber College. By the time I graduate from this course I intend to have a high understanding of both graphic and web/app design. I am now able to create a website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript from my learnings at Humber College.

Highlights of my skills include:

- Website, UX and GUI Design and Web Development: I am able to design a website from scratch.
- Create Interactive Media and Logo design
- Print and Digital Graphic Design: Logo, Stationery, Poster, Advertisement design
- Signage Design: Indoor and outdoor signage design, Banners, Flags

I believe I am a good fit for the role at the Legislative Assembly as I not only have the correct skills to carry out the work, but I also have experience in working with various clients and coworkers from different backgrounds in my previous job.

I would love to find out more about this amazing opportunity at Ontario's Legislative Assembly and let you know how I could benefit your organization.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to hearing from you.

Yours sincerely, Jinny An